Emily, it's out of control.
Yeah, I want to respond to what you were saying, Douglas,
which is so important.
And I think as we all talk about the horror that we feel
over the safety of these officers,
I want to illustrate a couple legal angles too,
because it's also about equal protection.
And this to me is creating sort of a giant legal mess
that renders us even more vulnerable.
And unlike JB Pritzker, I use words us,
because we are all Americans, right?
And we are all under the same flag.
And he continues using those pejoratives, and they,
and they, well, they are Americans tasked
with enforcing the laws that the legislature has passed.
So it's not just about officer safety.
It's about equal protection.
And thank God nothing happened to a federal officer
or a local officer, because I know for a fact
that if they had indeed been ordered to stand down,
that all of them felt with their souls
that it was crushing them to not render aid
and come to the aid of their fellow Americans
and their fellow brave Americans in uniform.
And if something had happened, they have a massive case.
This is deliberate indifference.
This is breach of duty.
And then we're sort of hearing, oh, no, no, no.
We didn't order that.
So then that to me becomes a PR nightmare.
And any criminal defense attorney will tell you
that that's creating this climate where then you can argue,
well, is there a bias?
Is there, again, that deliberate indifference?
Is there compromised investigation?
Has this been politicized?
So anything coming anywhere remotely
out of that jurisdiction I think is ripe for vulnerability.
It's not just about this case.
It's not just about this aggressive
and violent demonstration.
No, this is about the consequences
of having such a fractured identity,
not a unified front, and not realizing the force
for the trees, the decisions and consequences.
Go beyond a soundbite or click on your Instagram.
It actually has real world legal consequences.
And by God, if those consequences are physical,
then it's something that America cannot sustain.
Look, last quick thought from you, Douglas,
on technically creating a no zone inside
of a sovereign nation against law enforcement.
Yeah, it's outrageous.
And it's been going on for years.
And it should have stopped years ago.
You cannot have effectively militia,
which is what these groups like Antifa are.
They are militia on American streets.
And every time Democratic lawmakers
have been told about this, they say the same thing.
They say things like either it's not happening
or what we see with our own eyes isn't being seen,
isn't real, or they say things like,
well, anti-fascist sounds good.
Who isn't anti-fascist?
You go, this group is a fascist group.
They literally dress in black block.
They attack and hospitalized journalists.
They will go out of their way to attack federal officers,
police, ICE, and others.
And we just saw the other day with the shooter
in California who fired his rifle at ICE agents.
He killed two detainees.
But he was firing live rounds at ICE officers.
This is going to get worse if this is not finally countered.
All right, we'll move forward.
The would-be assassin of Justice Brett Kavanaugh
has been sentenced to just eight years and one month
behind bars.
And the Justice Department says that is not enough
and now is ready to take action.
We'll get into it.
Stay close.
Hey, everyone.
I'm Emily Campagno.
Catch me and my co-hosts Harris Faulkner and Kaylee McEnany
on Outnumbered every weekday at 12 PM Eastern, or set your DVR.
Also, don't forget to subscribe to the Fox News YouTube
page for daily highlights.